play.vg 2010-05-22

# play.vg Privacy Policy

**Warning** : include(/468adsense.php) [function.include]: failed to open stream: No such file or directory in **/home/goplay/public_html/content_start.php** on line **26**

**Warning** : include() [function.include]: Failed opening '/468adsense.php' for inclusion (include_path='.:/usr/lib/php:/usr/local/lib/php') in **/home/goplay/public_html/content_start.php** on line **26**

play.vg Privacy Policy

Special note to game authors: If your game is being used on this site and you want it removed please contact me and it will be removed immediately! I apologise for any inconvenience this may have caused you.

Visitors: Your privacy is important to us. That is why no personal information is collected about you by vgstores.com. No information about specific visitors is ever tracked or stored. However, general, non-personal data (such as the type of web browser you are using for example) may be logged for aggregate statistics data. This information is used to ensure that the site is compatible with the majority of visitors.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this website. Google's use of the [Doubleclick DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

This site, play.vg, may at the current time use the services of one or more advertisement brokers, which may include Burstmedia ([www.burstmedia.com](http://www.burstmedia.com/)), Google AdSense ([www.google.com/adsense](https://www.google.com/adsense)) and/or others for the serving and/or targeting of ads, promotions and other marketing messages. To do this, the advertiser(s) may collect anonymous data through the use of cookies. To learn more about Burstmedia, go to <http://www.burstmedia.com/release/about.asp>. To read Google's privacy policy, go to [news.google.com/privacy.html](http://news.google.com/privacy.html).

Any questions regarding this privacy policy should be directed to the webmaster at [webmaster@play.vg](mailto:webmaster@play.vg).

* * *

_Don't miss checking out the[Top 20 Gaming Sites](http://playvg.top20free.com/)!_ Play.vg Partner Sites  
---  
[DOS Games](http://www.dosgames.com/) | [Windows Games](http://www.play.vg/windowsgames/) | [Your site?](http://www.play.vg/link_to_us.php) | _!! !!!_
